let me leave appreciation allow me leave
acknowledgment
but where we have failed terribly is an
approach
is not enough to learn the duty of
Prayer
is not enough to learn how to pray
you must also learn how to approach God
does it make sense
because you're coming before who God
it's important
how you approach it else you may think
is there and he is not what
it's not that in the first place
I remember when he met Moses
at the burning bush
he told Moses hey
remove your
the place where you stand is what
Joshua
who takes over after who muscles
also
at some point when they're just about to
take over
um it's called what
Derek
he appears to Joshua
and Joshua thinks he's an enemy
and he tells Joshua I am the commander
of the army of what
of the Lord
remove your what
your shoes
where you stand
and so in as much as God is our father
we are his children
we cannot approach him the way we
approach and equal
there must be a sense of reverence
yes is my father I can talk to him tell
him what I want
it's like a son talks to his father
but you must remember the back of your
mind is not an equal to you
is The Sovereign God
supreme god
creator of the universe
reverence
is key
it has taught me even when I do my
prayers at the altar see the way you
wake up from bed we we with a a night
dress that reaches here
huh and then you say bedroom Young what
you forgot is that you are approaching
who
naked
yeah
even if your neighbor knocked if your
neighbor knocked in the middle of the
night and you are in that night dress
because it's you and your husband that
night dress do you go to open the door
without my dress
well do you open the door without my
dress
up
bedroom yeah
even the Lord had given directions on
how to build those altars our same text
let me just go back there before we we
we go to
to to what we want to learn today listen
verse 25 Exodus 20 24.
we are now in 25 and if you make me an
altar of stone
you shall not build it of healing stone
human Stone like like this ones
okay
uh
Stones
you shall not build it of him stones for
if you use your tool on it
if you use your tool on it you have Pro
profended
listen to 26 nor shall you go up by
steps to my altar it is not an altar you
build that you can you can step on As
you move to it why listen listen to the
reason why why that your nakedness may
not be exposed or not
foreign
to meeting our creator
very careless
we forget we are in the presence of God
how now
those are special moments
that you think twice before you kneel
down I'm coming in the presence of who
is the only beat we have not taught our
people
and so
when
Jacob
has just made peace
with his brother Esau
and remember they had a night they had
wrestled with God
and the Lord blesses him
and creates peace between him and his
brother
Jacob in chapter 33 verse 20.
the Bible says
Genesis sorry at the Jacob Genesis
then he erected an altar there
and called it El elohi Israel
and just when he had done that no
they've just met with the South they
have made peace and he's thanking God
that I've made peace with my brother he
erects an old to thank the Lord
chapter 34
he has not even settled
and then some two sons
circumcised
shekemites
this was simulant
and live
and Jacob is now afraid
that my we are a small people
these guys will gang against us and will
kill us and as to cry to the Lord what
to do next and the Lord tells him move
to bed
so we're in chapter 35.
then God said to Jacob
foreign
go up to where
to Bethel depends
I do that just to be sure that you're
with me
arise go up to Bethel
and dwell there
is
better
listen and make an altar there to
to God he's so specific because people
have risen people have have erected
altars to the devil he specifically say
God dwell there and make an altar to God
who appeared to you when you fled from
the face of iso your brother
I want to
to have you imagine Jacob
and his household his household
is more than you are
we are talking about the four women and
all their children
and all his servants
with their families and what
wives and
and children it's a big household
and these people
Jacob has to prepare them
for wasp
and when
follow me closer because if you don't
follow me closely you'll say
the Lord has told him you know Bethel is
not but Jacob Jacob Jacob is is so happy
very grateful how the Lord has dealt
with him
Jacob has been carrying a luggage on his
shoulder for a very long time
since he left his home when his mother
was alive
remember he came when his mother is dead
foreign
the day
he said the truth about his name is the
day the Lord
blessed him
I changed his name
so he's been carrying that luggage
for many years a young man who is not
married
now marries two women
takes house guards
again
foreign
there is no day you will convince a
child against their father or against
their mother at the end of the day they
know this is my mother
this is my father
you come Toto
subscribe
so the Lord blesses him
and so he sent his parents money home
and one day he says his mother told him
no react
able
subscribe
your Rachel Rachel was not Richard was a
squint
you know I squint
ing I want to
okay
so she didn't have the beauty to
to you know for a man that man would
like this is beautiful now
if anything Beauty they say lies in the
eyes of
foreign
he was also done what
I've always wondered how do you sleep
with a woman a whole night
without knowing
as two two women added two house girls
as children as workers Jacob's house is
big
ger
because
foreign
you pass it
[Music]
they always prepare someone that
will take over other times you are
unlucky you land on a woman
who's an inheritor of Witchcraft I tell
you you're a miserable man
your whole life you inherit all the
classes
the Bible does not call them wives
I'm offending some people but that is a
reality
so he might be being in it's
foreign
forward eagle
it's a whole mess in Jacob's life
foreign
situation needed God's intervention
if God was not going to intervene that
man was going to die either way
just a pleasure the stress the
depression
it's not easy being a polygamist
you and I know what is in our homes
where this polygon
right I
foreign
you'd rather have a man pulled
question yeah
[Music]
he wants to find peace with God
he realizes the only person that can
sort me out here is who
and at one point he sent everyone
inienda
[Music]
those are the moments you need personal
moments with God
foreign
they'll tell you no man can love to
to women but can have fun
with more than one woman
no man can love what
can have fun with more than what
happened
foreign
never
is
a sun
da refugee
upon equivalent
is
foreign
God granted His Wish
and the blessing he received
was not wealth
the blessing Jacob wanted was a
reconciliation with his brother
forgiveness for his own sin
and the lord gave it to him
and they made peace with his brother
and when they made peace with his
brother the altar he erected at El what
El
that name is
was to thank God for that favor
and then when he thought he had just
created peace with his brother I am just
beginning to settle boom
Simeon and Levy butcher a whole
community
and now he was scared I've been a man on
the run I'm now again a man on the Run
and he talks to his God and the Lord
tells him okay now what you do
go to where
it's about that and when you go there
you're going to dwell there
and as you dwell there build an award
so Jacob knows his carrying baggage and
luggage
that he must move with to go and worship
who God
and he must prepare his people
so as he prepares his people listen to
me my brother my sister
said
and Jacob said to his household
household
and to all who are with him
kilometer
put away
the foreign gods
that are among you
he's preparing them for worship
put away what
hey
what
of foreign gods that are money
purify your word
we'll get back there just put your
finger there was three then let us arise
he's preparing them on how you approach
God
then let us arise and go up to Bethel
and I will make an altar there to God
who answered me in the day of my
distress and has been with me in the way
which I have got so basically what he's
saying we are not going until you put
away all strange Gods until you change
your garments until you cleanse
yourselves
foreign because he knows we are going to
meet with who
so you remember I said when you build an
altar to the Lord you summon his word
his presence
first four
so they gave Jacob all the what honoring
Gods which were in there what
France and the earrings which were
either what yes and Jacob hid them under
the turbine tree tree which was by
Shekinah
we're moving slowly
number one
as he prepares to approach God
he told them put away all the foreign
question
which were the foreign gods
huh
which were the foreign Goods
someone is mammary
what are you saying
see and he give and they gave him all
the strange God that were
in their hands under what
basically all honor
so when when you put on Bangles
and and
I'll be called this then
what whatever whether it's p nor ring or
or or or piglet
this thing here they put on the other
arm
on the pigs or whatever you want to call
it
whether it's a stud it doesn't matter
the size whether it's just the size of a
DOT it doesn't matter it doesn't matter
all the the the necklaces that you put
on to work but when you come for choir
practice you remove them at the gate all
the anklets
you know it was strange word
and the other he says you should not
have
any other God be
that tells you when you have those
things
you have strange Gods so what happens
the Lord cannot manifest his presence
he can't
where there are strange gods that is why
when they went into Canaan and he told
them destroy
all altars
on
idos
foreign
the Lord can never manifest his presence
where there are strange Gods you
remember when they were going to Canaan
he told them if I go with you I will
consume you and Moses asked why and he
told them
all ornaments whatever yachty
Buddhism
foreign
[Applause]
the necklace
that is the same shock that God has when
he sees his children
because this is not his creation
a small thing to even come to church
with those things
it's not a small thing
not even in church every
everything if it does not fit charge it
doesn't fit
everywhere particularly when you know
you are the redeemed of the Lord
allow me stretch the least and it will
hurt you
whether it is lipstick
whether it is nail polish
whether it is eye pencil
well that is Mecca makeup is a Jezebel
spirit it is Jezebel that used to paint
her what
her face
it was a Jezebel spirit
women having to
wanting to look yellow
whether it is synthetic hair do you know
synthetic hair
week
we've
braids
idea
because you're carrying demonic power
not only on yourself but in your house
your territory is marked as demonic
territory
do you know why Legends again
is a territory they're marking for those
spirits that they believe they taught
so when they roam they know this is our
place
so when you have those things you're
marking your territory as a territory
for the devil he knows
yet
[Music]
foreign
chicken
one of them
is
what
Mama white says the head should ever be
kept cool
that is not as important to me as the
fact that what you're keeping on
yourself is an item that belongs to who
to the devil
and you want to use it to approach who
he will never show up
so the moment someone struggles to pray
and tells you illness is key
um
the temple this Temple is this body is
the Temple of the world
how do you want the spirit to dwell
together with other gods
it doesn't so you read Mama it says
elsewhere that these things we put on
the hair they prevent you from
Discerning sacred things
sacred things are spiritually I mean
spiritual things are spiritually
so you lack discernment and you cannot
discern sacred things simply because of
between
ah
ETI Rainbow Six
the day the Lord will give you a
spiritual eyes you will detest these
things to the Core
you just see it in the disgust
you'll see it in its true picture
and when I see some of us
[Music]
Jacob says
yeah
back up
we have also grown from the
also
I am a professional hairdresser so I
don't speak
because you think I are not I'm a
professional hairdresser
that once worked in high-end salons
so I know it matters here
it's not that I can't do my hair I'm on
payroll
and I make my own money elsewhere
so I can make my
but when I decided Omar when when I when
I learned that I cannot get a higher
anointing ah I cannot be Lord leave me
up and I shallower I shall stop I cannot
I cannot go beyond where I am in my
spiritual life simply because the things
I'm holding onto
and the Lord is saying I'm willing to go
with you but I can't because you've
refused to let go what this thing had to
let go
so when someone sits somewhere and say
she's a powerful preacher there are
things we have had to let what
for God
to use users we have had to be totally
sold out to God oh God to use this
and today in my house
we have tried
get read
of anything
that does not glorify God's name I was
only left with something called the TV
okina
Frozen
and my husband is kissy but with low
spirit
okay
so our TV spans almost the whole world
a big one
big one that
when we visit someone
we struggle to to because we're used to
just opening our eyes big
but when we learned this Slowly by
slowly together with our children one
day
we came home with my husband
and they said
we don't want the TV
anymore
they decided on their own
today if you come to my living room it's
not there
I'm using it in my bedroom
for my office issues
my husband uses it as a big screen
recording
it takes efforts
you must be in tension
deliberate
and then the Lord gives you the power
to do it
that is why
when you hear me before I preach asking
God to please just come down
I'm just pleading because I know he can
choose not to
based on all these things
that are on our heads here
he can choose not
and that is why many of our churches
are very cold
it's not cold
because
people are not strong
the strength is not in man
what what makes a church warm is the
presence of Heaven
what makes music
is that angels can join in the strain
but you see they cannot
because the environment does not work
paper
it's always struggle with God and I tell
him if you hear me pray heaven
and the heaven of Heavens cannot contain
you
and if he must come down he told Israel
if I continue cooking with you I will
consume you
because of these things you're having so
he chooses he knows I really want to
come down here but if I come he will
consume all of us
so you'd rather stay away
stay away
can you imagine how church would be
when you decide to get rid of everything
that is ungodly
I want you to imagine the presence of
Heaven in this church
no one would want to go home everyone
will come here by seven six people will
be here because they know the experience
they have when they come they know no
one is
foreign
[Music]
so it's not enough to build an altar for
the Lord
today today
get rid of it
you can't tell me if the experience is
the same
different
is that what God has with everyone
and it's the one that works both to Will
and to do
is good pleasure
he only needs a heart that is saying God
I submit to your work to your power
do as you please
number one
is
is that time you you struggle to pray
um
if I knew you lift you you lift your
your knees you feel like did I even talk
to God in the first place what did I
even say
ing
um
you are a don't
in the things of the world that belong
to the world of Darkness
let's get rid of it
where God manifests his presence you
will experience it
it's not an imagination
you'll experience
you will
and then it tells them
purify yourselves
it's time we confessed our sins
and purified ourselves from all outward
impurity
the Bible says the prayer of a righteous
man
Avail it
you cannot convince me you are an
ordained pastor
or an ordained Elder and convince me
that you can dedicate my child and
they're blessed
you you enjoying
okay
mama
of a righteous man
they let
much not every month of trees
his prayers are hard
let no one
mighty
and so we are going to approach God we
are going to make our prayers there
could be saying cleanse your thank you
cells
it's the same thing Israel was told when
they were approaching Jericho the Lord
told them tell Israel to cleanse
themselves
struggling with masturbation
that you're a married man married woman
all the secret scene
having sex with yourself it's called
solo sex
struggling with pornography
killing spouses out here
davolo told us told those that I can't
sex is not an art that you must be
taught out here
someone to tell you buy this book 101
Styles but
foreign
and you see couples watching pornography
in the name of trying to learn
how to get comfortable when getting
intimate
what they did know is as they watch porn
artists are never in the right senses
they're under the influence of drugs
and then you introduce funny things in
your house anal sex oral sex
and then before you know it because your
partner cannot perform as you watched
with her you become an addict of what
are you struggling to pull out
and where are any porn addict
cannot miss masturbation
the two go together
and when it becomes too much you get
into drug addiction
just to keep those things off your head
don't pretend
tell God I have this thing weighing me
down
because
our relative
ly
foreign
let's confess
cleansing yourself means
there's a sin
that you confess but you don't repent
this is a two different things people
have confessed sins but are unable to do
what
because repentance must issue in a
lifestyle
I was a gossiper
I have confessed God for sure
defend you cannot
foreign
what what is it
and then it tells him
change your what
is
[Applause]
the end
ing in English
foreign
every woman is struggling to serve high
table
just decently
you'll not come to God in these things
will come
it's the other day I learned and I'm
also growing in this Ellen White says we
cannot go to church with the clothes we
use in the course of the water
there must be a Sabbath suit
I'm struggling with that in my house
and I told God
is it's all about extravagance it's
about simplicity
just knowing Sabbath is special a
meeting with the Creator
but because it has never done in our
conscience that we are coming to meet
who no
same guys change your what
we cannot show up before the Lord
with these things we are putting up
your father passed Elizabeth
do you think the Lord would be pleased
to manifest his presence
do you think
do you think so
that is why many times we show up in
church and go back worse than we did
what
because the Lord didn't visit
he knows if you visit he will consume
all of us
so he would rather not
just watch and see how his children are
getting lost
so it's not just about raising an altar
is about knowing how to approach him on
that old
because it is him we are meeting
and then he says
so they gave Jacob all the foreign Gods
which were in their hands and the
earrings
which were in their ears and the Jacob
he demand of the turbine tree which was
by shechem listen to verse 5 and they
just
the Bible says and they did what they
journeyed and then
foreign
praise the Lord
listen what happened
when they learned how to approach god
listen what they happen and they
journeyed and the terror of God was upon
the cities that were all around them and
they did not pursue the sons of who
remember remember
Jacob Simeone
let me just go back to what the father
said well who knows that where we can
locate that that verse
um
what's that is it
yes then Jacob said to Simeon and Levy
you have troubled Me by making me
obnoxious to be obnoxious is to stink
by making me think among the inhabitants
of the land among the Canaanites
parasites and since I am few in number
took our church
I am few in the number they will gather
themselves together against me and kill
me let me ask you if you go in a foreign
land and kill people there
they know this is an enemy
to me
but look at what they did just by
preparing themselves to go and meet with
the Lord
took away all God's
changed their governments cleansed
themselves the Bible says the terror
of the Lord
was upon them
the cities that no one there had come
what
that Terror means simply the presence of
the Lord was with what
whether
what was
and there are very few
there are very few but no City could
come close because God was with
it tells you you do not know the God you
are doing what
the terror of God is not yet upon
foreign
is to make sure you have hidden yourself
in God
foreign
that will tell their client
IA Michigan
friends I wish you knew the experience
of Walking with God and experiencing his
presence real in your life you become a
terror
to the world
no one
comes close
you know what
and these are the women I've always
thought if you think you have a husband
who's a drunkard
huh
that is a demon
a demon of drinking
come on
the terror you post to the drunkard he
cannot even lift his hand
he can't he comes to his house drunk
I'm actually
um compound
is
it
submits to the power of who
and that is why I keep on telling people
marriage is a spiritual warfare
if you're not built spiritually don't
dare a man to beat you he will kill you
and they ask me should I go and I tell
them go go if you do not know the god of
the universe go if you have no
relationship with him you've never
experienced this power please go because
you will die for Facebook
does it have to come up to this point is
make sure
you know this God
not
a bunch of facts about it but you are in
an intimate
relationship with him one which is
reciprocal because it means the power
that Reigns within you
there is no demonic power that can come
close
and those are the women that survive
marriage
this ever married
foreign
money
because I cannot
come on
friends I don't know what I'm saying
things you don't understand
I'm sharing with you things I experience
but make me who I am today
if anything it pulls you away from who
what
the things of art will dim and lose
their
if we recall they only borrowed forward
[Music]
with the world of Darkness
it doesn't even last for long
does it
why should you load your hair with
things that add extra weight cut your
hairline until it reaches you
so now I'm asking have you been
investing in beauty or ugliness
begin to suffer hair loss
do you have baldness
oh mama
foreign
economics
if you understood what can be generated
from a proper home
you don't even wish employment
and don't misquote me not asking anyone
to
not to be a blood
I'm saying
I pray the Lord gives you
the eyes to see
what he sees
we will not run around the world chasing
nothing
so when people tell me Pastor please
talk to our children about lgbtq I have
nothing to say to your children but I
have something to say to you
because you you now you're now giving me
your luggage
which I cannot handle
come on
it terrifies when someone calls you and
says I've been married 17 years I just
noticed two years ago my husband is gay
two years ago and I'm like Mama this
thing didn't start two years ago it
started law you married a gay man
but it just came into
the open two years ago
did you want how do we help our children
any child you hold in your hand remember
will be someone's husband or someone's
what
just be careful as I struggle to raise
mine in the Lord struggle to raise your
son in the water
so that when they meet Joseph
mistake
I've been in marriage right now 19 years
there's no single day I have had
kiss
ES
because those are the children we are
raising
children we are raised children that
cannot think
they can't
they can't we met
asking you what are you raising
particularly for our sons
I need to raise strong daughters that
can raise strong children
I need to raise strong signs that can
take care of good families
so when you make noise out here about
men remember you have a son
Oma
um
I have a son that I wouldn't want to
turn out to be a cabbage I to 18 years
how now
how does an 18 year old ask me for
money to shave how how
kilometer
ha
um
my daughter cleared form four last year
I don't know mama if you need anything
from me
two months to exams
and I said I will struggle alone
so that
as she does exams at the back of her
mind she knows but
I told him
oh
nikona relief
stress
is
can you imagine
so nikians
to date this is now month what
month
no month five six month five she she
she's she's the house girl in my house
and I know she can hit me but she knows
and I operate in my house like I don't
know anything meaning
foreign
Sunday I'm on a mission
so she knows she knows if mommy is
leaving Sunday morning she knows
him
and I leave her the money
she shops every Sunday food for the
whole week
of fridge
foreign
because I know what life out here is
so why would I raise my child as if
things are easy
and they know all my children know
provided you have reached the age where
you can put your hand in the plate
and take to your mouth
he who does not work does not do it
is how we operate
the follow is a class five
the following is a class five and you
end your babysit
okay
foreign
and then they are twins for grade one
they work
so I struggle like this for them to meet
some funny boy from your house
I want to rest my case
and see how to go home now
so Jacob came to lose
that is better which is in the land of
Canon
he and all the people who were with him
and he built an altar there and called
the place Al better because their God
appeared to him when he fled from the
face of his brother
I've told you what I can't tell you
take it
live it
allow me entertain a few comments
and questions
a few comments
any questions
let me see the hands that I've
questioned because if one starts they
will all shoot up we will not finish
and I'm counting and if there is none
there's none
they are at work
are dreads also satanic very satanic
natural ones it doesn't matter
should we why I'm saying this
have an experience with Deliverance
prayers
okay
and demons at times would refuse to come
they say
dreads
the times we cut the minute you cut the
person is done what delivered
what I'm saying I'm saying whatever you
want to call Natural you want to call
what I know people have seen you on
social media with my tutors those are
days we didn't know
but we agree
just like any other person
I am saying
cultivate the highest level of
Simplicity try Remain the way the Lord
created
that that is the principle
did you know part one of the ways to
reduce stress in your life is to keep it
simple
just live a simple life
and you reduce a lot of stress in your
life
should we stop giving out money to our
wives for Salah
allow me to answer
if it is to acquire satanic things stop
if it's to acquire satanic things do
what
stop it nowhere to invest
and I've seen people crying over Hunger
but their hair is well done
um
I'm not saying you neglect yourself I'm
saying know what is priority in your one
who said Simplicity means looking weird
Simplicity means standing out as one
appointed to who to God
there's got to be a difference between a
redeemed one and a child of the world
we cannot be the same this must be a
distinction
so you need to choose whether you still
want to belong to them online
let me just do this except
um
is a is a periodical
a periodical called the health reformer
October 1871 if I'm not wrong
the periodical is entitled what what's
to
the political result reformer
the title is words to Christian what
mothers
it does not have pages
but I I am suggesting anyone who's a
mother read that okay the health
reformer October 1 1871 words to
Christian mothers
is all about
these things that bother us the hair the
war but allow me do do a paragraph here
go read all of it just go read all of it
just go read all of it listen listen
listen
fashion loads the heads of women with
artificial braids and pads
foreign
this is not Illinois speaking this is
God speaking through
Ellen why that this thing you think is
beautiful does not add to your word
you make yourself
ugly
which do not add to their beauty but
give an unnatural shape to the Head
and the ships are as many as the styles
the hair is strained is it
the hair is strained and forced into
unnatural positions and it is not
possible for the heads of these
fashionable ladies to be comfortable is
it possible foreign
thank you
the artificial hair
and pads covering the base of the brain
heat and excite the spinal nerves
centering in the brain
the head should ever be kept cool
ever
be kept what
what you finding
the heat caused by these artificials
induces the blood to the brain
the action of the blood upon the lower
or animal organs
or animal organs of the brain causes
unnatural activity it tends to
recklessness in morals and the mind and
heart is in danger of being corrupted
too much blood
causes a natural activity on the animal
organs the back brain so you're more
driven with emotions
than with sense
so that is
because you've been driven by what
happened
is
foreign
listen the action of the blood upon the
lower or animal organs of brain causes a
natural activity
thanks to recklessness in order
because it is not you thinking now your
brain has been captured taken captive
you cannot you cannot see sense
good is evil evil is good
and the mind and heart is in danger of
being corrupted as the animal organs are
excited and strengthened because you
excite the animal organs
the morals are in feebled the moral and
intellectual powers of the Mind the
moral and intellectual powers of the
Mind become servants to the animal now
listen in consequence listen to the
consequence in consequence of the brain
being congested it's now lose their
healthy action
and take on morbid conditions making it
almost impossible to arouse moral
sensibilities
such lose their power to discern sacred
what
things
that is only line I read
and I dropped it
that God is speaking I cannot hear him
because of my word
the unnatural heat caused by this
artificial deformities about the head
induces the blood to the brain producing
congestion and causing the natural hair
to fall off
huh
thus the natural is sacrificed to the
artificial many have lost their reason
and become hopelessly insane by
following this deforming fashion yet the
slaves of fashion to Fashion will
continue to dress to thus bless their
heads and the safariable horrible
disease and the premature death rather
than be out of
a physician writing a series of letters
to a school girl devotes one to the nice
keeping of the hair among other
directions he remarks that much is said
against wearing switches or juts or
chignons uh
dryers
okay see you know them
the dryers the Steamers the what
because they breed pestiferous women
whose life is fed by their dream on the
blood small blood vessels of the scalp
but all such objections to these
monstrosities become as nothing compared
listen you see it doesn't matter what
those things do they are not as
important to this main thing they do
listen to what they do the worst one
compared with the objection which arises
from the congested condition of the
blood vessels of the back brain by the
reason of their use and switch your
signals is a substance which in itself
is a great conduct of animal Heat
as the back of the head has a great deal
of blood and a great deal of blood as a
great deal of heat in it the Surplus
edge of this heat should be allowed to
pass off outwardly to wear one of these
appliances is to keep it in and as the
part that's dressed becomes excessively
heated
disease takes place in a little while
and the whole bodily structure becomes
affected listen in women
in women there is such an intimate
connection between the back brain and
the reproductive structure
connected
intimately you interfere with this
interfere with us
that when the former becomes and feebled
the back brain becomes amphibos
the latter invariably takes on morbid
conditions
are reproductive
is it worth it
so are you investing in beauty or
rottenness
so the man that is asking should we stop
giving our wives money to the sun please
because this is what it does
to your wife
and you think it's Beauty it's not
Beauty
is
yes
Elder is really trying to convince me
that some are just repeating themselves
is it wrong for men to plait their hair
yes
stop it
even this hash none is
this thing nowadays you shave here and
leave some here
you will not understand what I'm saying
because probably most of you have not
reached that level that you can
understand what I'm saying but wait
until you begin Warfare in the world of
Darkness then you'll understand what we
say
what about mohawk for women Wacha
bald shaving for men I don't know where
it came from
it was it was fashion from
where did Bal shaving come
what I know
there is a function that the hair plays
on the
on the skull
so that you don't need to cut all
all of it
you don't need to
I'm just saying it
politely
I mean many men would want to contest
this but but it's good leave a little
word
live a little just just a little little
hair okay just just leave a little go
study the function of the hair itself so
that you don't have to to chop all of
all of it I know it's a fashion that
came when
when someone died some celebrity had
died
and people just started cutting
it was even there in the Egyptian
culture
that the things we have adopted
normalized and accepted and and we think
is not
just just leave some some little
don't shave all of it
what is the danger
of what love to Facebook than what
than Bible
so what are you getting from this book
you know you cannot compare the Bible
and what
they don't address the same thing
they don't
and if there are things the devil has
hooked us into so that to distract us
from God is such a word
social media it has given you a false
perception of what life is all about and
I see people posting things families
wives children people pose like they're
okay until everyone say I want to be
like so and so
um
people people on Facebook for validation
that there's something missing in in
their life they're struggling with
things
not everyone I'm saying most of us want
validation
it's my birthday so what
help me wish my husband a birthday and
then what happened
it's our anniversary so that we do what
I wish the rate at which we were posting
personal things
would be the same rate we post business
business huh
we encourage each other to do business
serious things
WE Post evangelism business
opportunities
but people post nothing because
themselves they're full of what
then you find a good Adventist girl gone
to gone to a studio
with with address that when she's in
church she covers with Alice but in the
studio when she sits on that seat all
her ties are out Allah
they take comfort in those comments at a
beautiful
congratulations gorgeous tell me how
much money it has put in your account
nonsense
foreign
there's a difference between a producer
and a consumer
an employee and an employee
and most of people who do those things
actually employees and consumers
because when you are a producer you have
no time for those kinds of things
in fact you don't care who likes you and
who hates you
you move
some of us have learned to move whether
there is a like or it's not like people
comment say all manner of stuff we don't
care we don't know you have a problem go
deal with your problem
I don't need to validate myself on
social media
live acquired
quiet life
foreign
but because we post our emptiness
with a desire to be validated
and then we are so dry and thirsty and
empty in the matters of who God
and then someone says me I can't even
read the Bible and four straight hours
just responding to things or not
Facebook Twitter
other people's lives
talk about men addicted to Facebook than
the Bible why men
anyone who's addicted why men
anyone can fall a victim of this
addiction
I've seen women employing house girls
just to have time on what
Facebook
anyone
I guess this is a woman complaining
either the husband has too much time on
Facebook
done on her so she would rather she
would rather have a hooked on the bahi
book than what
the Facebook
there is a there's a trust in man
can never be quenched by anything in
this world
save Christ himself
and because the devil knows it it is
Christ that can quench it he has given
us all manner of distractions
all manner
of distractions
this Society needs thinkers Not Mere
reflectors
but because we have not been raised
thinkers
thinking becomes a problem in our lives
that wants to engage your mind
creatively analytically
stress
anything that just want to tax your mind
a little bit
that would would require your creativity
your analytical beat you know
everyone switches off
we are used to people thinking
for us
and I ask
it is because our mind is packed with a
lot of garbage
fed with nonsense
there is a wisdom that only Heavens can
give the fear of the Lord
it's the beginning of what
tell you when you're in love with the
Lord you can never fail to be a thinker
the wisdom you have is not of this Earth
wisdom you have
is Heavenly
There is No Child of God deeply Must In
Christ that is not a thinker
no child okay
but when you realize you have no time
for God you can never be a thinker you
are full of drama
always
arguing even things that cannot be
should not be argued
because I shouldn't be again
very small things
I know you want an okay from me me I'll
not give you an okay I said just try
look the way the Lord did what
I want us to imagine we are going to
heaven tell me who's going to have a
nosy
I'm at dreadlocks
when someone dies do they do they are
they parted with those things
hello Pastor please advise on building
home altars if the husband is not
interested on things with worship
how do you encourage him to take the
lead I said most of these things you
fight them on your what
on your knees you don't push anyone
don't go like Pastor Elizabeth
you don't go home like that
these things are fought on the world
those that know my testimony on social
media
it's just this year my husband set an
old in our house himself
DC
and he runs it from wherever he is
Faithfully
all these years
I have taken lead with my children
because I didn't know God
many people ask me and I laughed they
think if you are a pastor your husband
when give it to Tomato company I always
tell them he's not even close to a
deacon Valley
but the Johnny God that has had with us
it is worth it
so when I tell you an altar that her
husband has raised is different from the
one my frustrated
and there is no day I ever sat with him
to discuss let's have an old no he just
hears me pretty good
[Music]
the way it would work on any other
individual it should work on it the rest
I finish on my what
is because you don't want to challenge
the head of the house over his
leadership you don't have you ever
challenged to see your CEO
um
consider yourself
it's things we fight them on our knees
because you can the work of convicting a
heart does not belong with a human being
the work of convicting the heart belongs
with the holy word
that is the person
that is the person you played with
and before you know it because the Lord
cannot give you what you have not asked
ask and I shall give and we don't ask
we fight
this is
foreign
what should one do in a case where the
husband left and remarried should one be
married afresh
or should stay single
I love Christians they create a mess
then they want you to give them a
solution
foreign
and those are questions that put me in a
straight place
okay
it's like God saying do not
do not eat this fruit
and then they go ahead and do what and
then they come back and ask the past
my husband and I ate the fruit what is
your advice
there are consequences
that we would love to live with
very difficult
and you know what that kind of life
looks like so you know it
it's not easy
it's not
it comes heavy
we can avoid it
two wrongs don't make
a right some of they do but he's moved
on
if you believe you are truly married to
that man then there's nowhere you're
going
you begin your own battle there
because for me I believe there is only
one spiritual Covenant one spiritual
marriage covenant that is recognized in
a way in heaven
so this other one side shows that
someone leaves and gets someone else
they go I've always likened it to to to
fueling a gas law
with with 200.
and expecting it
to reach Chinese
I told you spiritual warfare
it is hard for the one that does not
know God for the one that knows God it
is your prayer that brings that man
backward
s
your prayer is the one that brings him
back home
because we are not grounded in Christ
it's difficult for us to fight this the
best solution is also for us to say I
have moved on
and then many who move on because they
already have children they go become
second wives in another marriage
backwards
these are not easy questions
there's a way the Lord wants us to live
and then we mess and then we want
solutions for our what
comes with the repercussions
and we learn to go through it
don't create another mess
if my husband impregnates a girl should
he marry her to be the head of the altar
foreign
even with those flows
even with those flaws there is no one
Beyond God's power to redeem
no one
and if you think you can write off
people like that you can
you can you know what what you people
are saying is you you're married to
angels that don't make mistakes
and there's a sin that cannot be
tolerated
in fact you need to ask yourself
week three nickel periods
week four never talk
to me go on
kichwa
um
and then we blame it on someone else
attacking It Is Us
amazing
that feed on this thing anytime is tea
time
you have set the example in your house
with seductive dressing so when your
house girl comes they copy the Sunday
what you forget your house girl has
shaped and you
so when you when you're in the house and
you're with your tights and and the
t-shirt that reaches here
fast forward second floor you know
of
you know you have set the peace
for members of your heart
so your daughter will dress like that
your house girl will do it
is
men go with what
site
as we go with touch
let me tell you even if he is saved
even if he saved
do not create a seductive environment in
your what
yes
the Bible says Abram was a man who was
able to command his household after him
you don't tell Abraham the kind of life
you live in his home state
you don't
so most of us have set that bad pace
and we have had relatives friends
house guns in our house trans
seductively
at times is a very short skirt tight lit
here
your husband feeds on it every day
he drives on the road the road is
seductive the office is seductive the
house is super seductive
questions
ah
is
some of these things we created award
credit ourselves
we do
now cubles
Your Story one month two months three
months or months but you're not staying
with a woman
you're staying with the word
um
is it right to bring a kid born out of
wedlock to be brought up with the
matrimonial kids while the mom is still
alive I don't know the arrangement you
have
I have no idea
but rarely would a woman leave his child
to go and
stay in another home
unless something happens
you have a woman who does not care about
her children
are the ones that would give you her
children what they would demand is
Sue
but if that opening is there what is the
problem
attitude brought up to be brought up
with the matrimonial kids so you think
if the matrimonial kids those ones are
Goods
okay
please share your contact I tell that's
a question share your contact can a Boy
Child be delegated a house cause like
cooking and cleaning this looks like a
cultural question why not
what is the problem
in learning how to cook
how to clean
so if I have a sense let me say I have
sons
I will raise them as men
there's nothing wrong in them knowing
how to do it
you mean I don't know how many times my
husband has gotten into the kitchen
willingly
this cooked porridge
the problem comes when a woman insists
that a man must work in the house that
is where the problem is
but are there times when no man is very
sick
and what's happening
foreign
even my twins I raced on nappies
it does not make him a lesser man
but I'm saying I must raise my voice to
be mad
at University let me just ask Sai Amanda
University
foreign
when my husband's phone has a password
does it mean that he keeps secret hey
what are you looking for in this form
not afternoon
is insecurity
we don't put passwords on phone
because we are keeping
Secrets there are many other reasons why
we put password on what
even on our laptops don't we put
passwords because we are keeping secrets
no
why are people always thinking on the
side of
evil
hi
that is an insecure
faster
which secret now
I don't know whether I'm the one who
lives a Carefree life
if you have a secret
let me ask you something if someone has
a secret what is a secret let's start
there what is the secret
what is the secret
something that only you so how does okal
know that there is something about
everybody knows
if if a secret if someone has a secret
well no
um
I don't know whether you're getting what
I'm saying
the only person that can know a secret
that is kept is who
the rest can only imagine
that there is a word
because that is why it is called award
Mama white says this
love begets love
trust begets what
just learn to trust people
with time
they will learn to to trust you
that that kind of life you want live it
fast leave it yourself
the rest will
your spouse will be asking
why is it her phone
is always just open
but you don't start
imagine
let me tell you if you want a beautiful
life in marriage
don't don't drive
your life based on
materialism and consumerism
if those things Max make a lot of sense
to you you will never thrive in marriage
let your greatest desire
be that my spouse is deeply in submerged
in Christ
the minute they know Christ so well the
rest falling out
let that be your greatest desire
watch
did you wear your secrets
let your greatest prayer desire be that
God
I pray that
my husband knows because the day your
husband will know God adultery will go
on occasion will go Secrets will go
those things don't go because you've
asked people to let them go no those
things go because there is another power
that operates in one
I don't know whether I'm the one who was
raised a fool
my husband will tell you I don't probe
I can see something
and I've trained myself it will not even
hurt me why why
life is not that serious there's a
heaven to come
I've trained myself that to
um
I miss you
he knows I don't probe
I will not even ask
because
[Music]
why is it you don't ask certain
questions
I don't and my prayer for all the years
I've known my husband was that God
I pray you incline his heart to yourself
that he may be able to keep your
Commandments your judgments and your
statutes if I can have that version of
mokoro I have the best husband in this
world
and slowly
it is paying off so when I tell you my
husband wakes me up at 3
from whatever is is time for devotion
and we do a three-hour
up to six
foreign
it paid off
we could be having lots of scars
looking back lots of bruises but they
remind us that we were once in America
and the Lord reached out his hand
and pulled us out
it reminds us of the power of God we
have experienced in person to get us to
where are we
it reminds us there are battles we
fought and we emerged Victorious
so we are more interested in the version
We are Becoming than in what we are and
what we used to
and what drives us is the desire to know
Christ deeply
the rest
we don't fight off
because at the back of my mind I know my
husband does not sustain me I am
sustained by God in a way
whatever
let no one lie to you that I can't live
without you you can
the only person you cannot live without
is who
he says without me you can do
when did it become that without
Elizabeth you can do nothing why
without mokuro you can do nothing
and that's why when you're left
stage
I'm just giving you an imagination okay
foreign
I can do all things through Christ who
doesn't
in Christ I am more than a word
yeah
he was out of his senses
and then the Bible says when he came to
his word
[Music]
foreign
don't say a lot of things
out there he would have died
the Lord sustained him because of the
prayer you have been making
many men out here play a lot out here
they don't get sick not because they use
condoms
they don't get sick because their wives
are on their watch
so you can choose how you want to fight
this but
foreign
and
but all that rubbish left out there
is a scar
that will remind you you fought a what
and you won it
I'm saying so heavy things some are
saying mama not to enjoy
I pray the Lord will speak to us
give us a better understanding that I
would want than I would want
us to understand may the Lord bless us
in Jesus name
thank you
get to the point take a step forward